<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
    <SHG_HeroEnd>With most of the League of Villains leaders dead and their hidden base destroyed the Hero Organization will be free to expand and chase out any remaining groups of Villains and bandits.\n\nThank you for playing the Superhero Genes mod! Once this popup is closed you'll be able to continue your colony with all your pawns that survived the final confrontation, so you can destroy some more villain settlements or go for another victory. Please make sure to give the mod a thumbs up in the workshop if you enjoyed it to make it more likely that others will have a chance to see the mod.\n\nIn the future I plan on making things like implants and drugs that will make it possible for non-supers to stand a better chance against supers, as long as the colony is willing to pay the price.</SHG_HeroEnd>
    <SHGHero_DestroyedDevices>Subdevices destroyed</SHGHero_DestroyedDevices>
    <SHGHero_DeviceDestroyed>Subdevice destroyed</SHGHero_DeviceDestroyed>
    <SHGHero_DeviceFoundLocation>You've finally learned the location of the central device!</SHGHero_DeviceFoundLocation>
    <SHGHero_DeviceFoundLocationFoundSecurityThreats>The device is housed in a large villain complex. You should expect heavy resistance as this is a very important place to {0}.</SHGHero_DeviceFoundLocationFoundSecurityThreats>
    <SHGHero_ThreatsDistrubed>The {0} have noticed your presence and are moving to get rid of you!</SHGHero_ThreatsDistrubed>
    <SHGHero_ThreatsAlerted>The {0} have been alerted to your presence.</SHGHero_ThreatsAlerted>  
    <SHGHero_ThreatsWaking>The villains will arrive in {0}</SHGHero_ThreatsWaking>
    <SHGHero_ThreatsWakingDesc>The villains will arrive in {0}. They will attack any who may threaten the device.</SHGHero_ThreatsWakingDesc>


        <!--Settings stuff-->
    <SHG_Heroes_ModName>Superhero Genes - Hero Organization</SHG_Heroes_ModName>
    <SHG_Heroes_ModDescription>When evil super-powered beings control the land, it is only natural that good super-powered people will band together to fight back. The Hero Organization is a group dedicated to fighting supervillains and any other group that aims to harm the innocent, and will do eveything in its power to ensure the crimes commited by The League of Villains in the past will not happen again.\n\nThe Hero Organization looks favorably on those who destroy the settlements of "evil" factions, and will regularly give quests to fight said factions, especially the League, and to hopefully save people in the process.\n\nThird mod of the Superhero Genes series.</SHG_Heroes_ModDescription>

    <SHG_MedievalHeroes>    Medieval Heroes (Restart Required)</SHG_MedievalHeroes>
    <SHG_MedievalHeroesDescription>Heroes and pawns from minor super groups will only use equipment with a technology level of medieval or lower.</SHG_MedievalHeroesDescription>
</LanguageData>
