<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Superhero Genes - Hero Organization</name>
  <author>alite</author>
  <packageId>SuperheroGenes.Heroes</packageId>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>ludeon.rimworld.biotech</packageId>
      <displayName>Biotech</displayName>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>SuperheroGenesBase.Mod</packageId>
      <displayName>Superhero Genes - Base</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2980061828</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>SuperheroGenes.Villains</packageId>
      <displayName>SHG - Villains and Stereotypes</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3088653906</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>

  <loadAfter>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Anomaly</li>
    <li>SuperheroGenesBase.Mod</li>
    <li>SuperheroGenes.Villains</li>
  </loadAfter>

  <description>
This requires [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3088653906]Villains and Stereotypes[/url] because it needs to reference multiple parts of that mod, most notably the League of Villains is a target of many quests, Some of the backstories are used for both factions, and the xenotypes are used by all of the pawns.

When evil super-powered people roam the land, it is only natural that other super-powered people will oppose them. These heroes banded together to create one large organization strong enough to fight evil in all its forms, The Hero Organization. This mod adds a new hero faction that you can align yourself with to fight The League of Villains, along with the ability to add some minor super hero groups that often offer a super creating pill variant or two with their merchants. 

When Royalty is active, this also offers new quests. Two of them are generic quests, one from each major super faction, that send you to a site to attack a team from the other faction, and are usually given once or twice per year to provide a regular source of infamy and valor. The Hero Organization also offers an end-game quest to your colony to help them stop The League's plan to wipe out the world by destroying some villainous devices. There is a setting you can enable that causes The League to start their plan on their own after 4 years, causing everyone in the world to die on the fifth year unless you intervene. This is disabled by default as it is not usually a fair fight.

[url=https://discord.gg/fYP8qkcNDh]Discord link[/url] for those who want an easier way to ask questions, make requests, or just chat. I'll also be posting new releases there.

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/alite/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]Easy link to all of my Rimworld mods[/url]

[url=https://github.com/KonradHeinser/][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url]
[url=https://ko-fi.com/alite56114][img]https://i.imgur.com/Utx6OIH.png[/img][/url]
  </description>
</ModMetaData>
